<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mere Vehicles</title>
    <link>https://merevehicles.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mere Vehicles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 19:15:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://merevehicles.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Clark</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/richard-clark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 19:15:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/richard-clark/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;[&amp;hellip;] media are mere vehicles that deliver instruction but do not influence student achievement any more than the truck that delivers our groceries causes changes in our nutrition&amp;rdquo;” (Clark 83: 445) or more subtly that “ there is strong evidence that many very different media attributes accomplish the same learning goal” and therefore: “ It there is no single media attribute that serves a unique cognitive effect for some learning task, then the attributes must be proxies for some other variables that are instrumental in learning gains” (Clark 1994:22).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thirteenth Tale</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/page-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 18:03:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/page-two/</guid>
      <description>Mauris sit amet urna sed sem dapibus volutpat vel non ipsum. Integer et dui ut sem ultricies efficitur nec nec ante. In non est erat. Duis porta, urna eget euismod placerat, enim nisl lacinia quam, vitae laoreet arcu ipsum non massa. Phasellus interdum enim eu semper egestas. Nulla facilisi. Fusce volutpat tincidunt erat. Quisque vehicula nulla id tortor volutpat venenatis in non magna. Sed imperdiet augue eget feugiat elementum. Aliquam commodo tellus eget placerat auctor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Page</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/sample-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 17:12:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/sample-page/</guid>
      <description>Hugo 0.24 Released: Big archetype update + @Netlify _redirects etc. file supporthttps://t.co/X94FmYDEZJ #gohugo #golang @spf13 @bepsays
&amp;mdash; GoHugo.io (@GoHugoIO) June 21, 2017  It was November. Although it was not yet late, the sky was dark when I turned into Laundress Passage. Father had finished for the day, switched off the shop lights and closed the shutters; but so I would not come home to darkness he had left on the light over the stairs to the flat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 15:55:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>In pulvinar orci quis convallis tincidunt. Nunc suscipit est ut massa rutrum rhoncus. Ut turpis lacus, sagittis ut convallis et, aliquam et leo. Ut ac sapien id est pulvinar laoreet. Sed porttitor turpis nunc, et accumsan lorem scelerisque at. Mauris ornare nulla eu tellus fermentum porttitor. Curabitur nisi nunc, sollicitudin sed tristique id, placerat porta augue. Etiam sed eleifend erat.
 Pellentesque eros ante, faucibus vitae accumsan non, tincidunt sollicitudin sem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>