<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mere Vehicles</title>
    <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mere Vehicles</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 19:15:20 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://merevehicles.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Clark</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/richard-clark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 19:15:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/richard-clark/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;[&amp;hellip;] media are mere vehicles that deliver instruction but do not influence student achievement any more than the truck that delivers our groceries causes changes in our nutrition&amp;rdquo;” (Clark 83: 445) or more subtly that “ there is strong evidence that many very different media attributes accomplish the same learning goal” and therefore: “ It there is no single media attribute that serves a unique cognitive effect for some learning task, then the attributes must be proxies for some other variables that are instrumental in learning gains” (Clark 1994:22).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Thirteenth Tale</title>
      <link>https://merevehicles.com/posts/page-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 18:03:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://merevehicles.com/posts/page-two/</guid>
      <description>How long did I sit on the stairs after reading the letter? I don&amp;rsquo;t know. For I was spellbound. There is something about words. In expert hands, manipulated deftly, they take you prisoner. Wind themselves around your limbs like spider silk, and when you are so enthralled you cannot move, they pierce your skin, enter your blood, numb your thoughts. Inside you they work their magic. When I at last woke up to myself, I could only guess what had been going on in the darkness of my unconsciousness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>